East of Eden: Art in Search of Life is a documentary film directed by None.
Herself, played by Susan Schillinglaw.
Himself, played by Thomas Steinbeck.
Himself, played by Richard Schickel.
Himself, played by William Bast.
Herself, played by Julie Harris.
Himself, played by Lonny Chapman.
The tree of life is a fundamental archetype in many of the world's
mythological, religious, and philosophical traditions.
It is closely related to the concept of the sacred tree.
The tree of the knowledge of good and evil and the tree of life which appear in Genesis' Garden of Eden as part of the Jewish cosmology of creation, and the tree of knowledge
connecting to heaven and the underworld such as Yggdrasil, are forms of the world tree or cosmic tree, and are portrayed in various religions and philosophies as the same tree.